const STORE = [
    {
      question: 'When was Fortnite Battle Royale released?',
      answers: [
        'September 2017',
        'June 2017',
        'April 2016',
        'October 2017'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'September 2017',
    },
    {
      question: 'What was the first cosmetic item a player could get?',
      answers: [
        'Pickaxe',
        'Umbrella',
        'Glider',
        'Character Skin'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Umbrella',
    },
    {
      question: 'How much damage does a headshot from a Golden Scar deal',
      answers: [
        '50',
        '64',
        '72',
        '70'
        ],
        correctAnswer: '72',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who won the Fall Skirmish',
      answers: [
        'Zexrow and Vinny1',
        'Tfue & Cloakzy',
        'Nate Hill & FunkBomb',
        '72hrs & Chap'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Tfue & Cloakzy',
    },
    {
      question: 'How many different shotguns have there been throughout all of fortnite?',
      answers: [
        '3',
        '8',
        '5',
        '4'
        ],
      correctAnswer: '5',
    },
    {
      question: 'What season was the Reaper skin from?',
      answers: [
        'Season 1',
        'Season 2',
        'Season 3',
        'Season 4'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Season 3',
    },
    {
      question: 'How many different snipers have there been throughout all of fortnite?',
      answers: [
      '3',
      '4',
      '5',
      '8'
      ],
      correctAnswer: '5',
    },
    {
      question: 'What was the community given name for the purple Cube from season 5?',
      answers: [
        'Eric',
        'Kevin',
        'Waldo',
        'Ralph'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Kevin',
    },
    {
      question: 'What season was the Mako glider released?',
      answers: [
      'Season 1',
      'Season 2',
      'Season 3',
      'Season 4'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Season 1',
    },
    {
      question: 'What was the first gun ever ‘vaulted’ in Fortnite Battle Royale?',
      answers: [
        'Zaptron',
        'Submachine gun',
        'Crossbow',
        'Smoke Grenades'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Zaptron',
    }
];